Hi, in this quick tutorial, I'm going to
show you how to use the subtasks feature
in Blitzet. This feature is great when
you need to split tasks into smaller
steps. First, let's add a subtask. To do
this, simply hover over any task in your
list. You'll see a little subtasks icon
appear, click it, and a drop-down will
expand. Now, type the title of your new
subtask and hit
enter. And there you go. Subtask is
added. You can add more in the same way.
Managing your subtasks is easy, too. If
you want to reorder them, just hover
over a subtask and use the up or down
arrows to move it within the list. And
if you want to delete a subtask, just
click the trash icon. The subtasks
feature helps you visually track your
progress step by step. When you finish a
subtask, click the check box next to it
to mark it as done. You can see how the
progress dial updates instantly. It
shows how many subtasks you've completed
so
far. Now, what about when you're in
blitzet mode? It works the similar way.
You can see the list of subtasks by
pressing the arrow button, and you can
add the new ones by pressing the plus
button, even while you are in focus
mode. Currently, you need to have at
least one subtask added to a task in
order to view and update subtasks in
focus mode. Oh, and one more cool thing.
If you use notion and integrate it with
Blitzet, any checkbox properties in your
notion databases can be synced directly
as subtasks in Blitzet. Let's go back to
list view so I can show you an example.
Here you can see I have a task
integrated from notion together with
subtasks synced. Please note that synced
subtasks cannot be deleted from Blitzet
since they are linked to your notion
data. Let me show you this feature in
action within notion itself. You'll see
how your updates in Blitzet are
replicated here. Currently, notion is
available as an integration and very
soon we excited to roll out new
integrations that will include ClickUp,
Trello and other
platforms. So that's it. I hope that was
helpful and clear for you. And if you
have any questions, proposals, ideas, or
would like to share your own
productivity tips, feel free to join our
Discord community. And stay tuned. A lot
of new features are coming.